In the tool bar, you can find the tool group of the retopo, click on the scissors to read the list.
Now when creating a smart retopo, it can be absorbed into the inner line or the inner shape.
The assist retopo point can now appear on the internal line of the retopo.
Just like the awl curve, the smart retopo can now be absorbed into the凸 curve.
The retopo line created can now be absorbed into the inner line and the inner shape.
This is the result of the retopo.
Use the Y and U keys to quickly switch between the edit tool and the create tool.
Use the create tool to click on the Ctrl and Shift keys to add a row to separate the top face.
Use the create tool to create a top point on the top face that has already been created, and then cut the top face.
Use the edit tool to drag the mouse to select or cancel the selected point.
Thank you for watching and see you in the next video!